[{"answer": "It is over in the sense that whatever we're talking about, we're talking about a period of transition until you get to elections.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "What happens next?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, Mubarak has appointed a vice president, Omar Suleiman, who is head of his intelligence -- who's been his intelligence chief for years.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you see anybody emerging, Anderson, tonight as a potential candidate to take over for Mubarak?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "People are enormously energized by the fact that they've found their voice, for the first time in 30 years, and they're not placated.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Describe what you've seen and what you think is going to happen next?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I sure wouldn't want to make a prediction about how long Mubarak is going to last, but what I do think is that right now, he has become an impediment to stability in Egypt.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "I mean, would you think from what you just said that Mubarak may be lucky to survive even the week?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it's passing.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "And are you picking up any sense of anti-Americanism?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Very well, Piers.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Mr. Blair, how are you?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "It's been a while.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "How are you doing?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "They are extraordinary times.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "These are pretty extraordinary times, aren't they?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Nobody seems quite sure what to say about President Mubarak.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "And in particular, I think the key challenge for us, really, is how do we help partner this process of change and help manage it in such a way that what comes out of it is open-minded, fair, democratic government?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Well, where you stand on him depends on whether you've worked with him from the outside or on the inside.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Where do you stand on him?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's true.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Of course I don't want to see that in any government.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Presumably, you would be critical of that kind of behavior by any government, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "You weren't proud before?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "And now you're proud?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, some do, some don't.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "How do you feel being a peace envoy in an area of the world where a lot of Arabs don't trust you and don't like you?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "It's a much better way.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Isn't it a better way to secure regime change than declaring war on countries?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Well, I think it all plays out depending on whether, as I say, the modernizing forces, the people who want, you know, the types of things we take for granted in Britain and America, and whether they are the people that would succeed those governments, or whether the very strong Islamist movements wouldn't rather take control.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "How do you think this is all going to play out?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Yes, but that in a sense is a healthy thing.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Isn't that the fear for all these -- all these governments in the Middle East now?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "It's extremely difficult to tell.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Finally, Mr. Blair, do you believe in your position as Middle East peace envoy, do you believe that peace is now more or less likely the way things stand today?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, that's something with he and his government and the people are going to have to decide.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Is that position tenable, do you think, given the reaction on the ground?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I'm not in the vice president's shoes, so I'm not going to --", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "If you'd been asked, as Vice President Biden was asked, is he a dictator, what would you have said?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "He's the leader of his country.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Let me ask you as Governor Romney, is he a dictator?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, they want to know that the America people stand with the voices of freedom and democracy.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "They see him as a dictator and they want someone in America to actually stand up for them, don't they?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Well, there's always been a bit of a potential conflict and a balance between two of our interests in foreign policy; one being that we support values and principles they are consistent with our own.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "hasn't that game now run its course?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, it was just a few weeks ago.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "But what was your take on what was going on there when you were there?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, what happened in Tunisia is having a seismic effect on what's happening throughout the Middle East.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Were you surprised?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "I don't have an answer for you yet, because there are a lot of things you have to consider before you make that final decision.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Yes or no, are you going to run for the presidency again?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "No, I don't have a 100 percent answer ready to go.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Am I right in thinking you know the answer, you just don't want to give it to me yet?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not somebody who can analyze for you the politics.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Does you and your position now emerge as the savior, if you like, of all this polarizing?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I believe she's an extraordinarily powerful and effective voice in our party, that she has generated a great deal of support and attention, that she'd be great in a primary process.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What do you believe about Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I don't know the answer to that.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Could you beat her?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "She probably does.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Does your wife know the answer to that?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not sure she knows whether I can win or lose.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "She thinks you can beat everyone, doesn't she?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, I think people would -- particularly my family, would disagree with that conclusion.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "I mean, you're pretty perfect, aren't you?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Do you still stand by every word of that?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Once again, I can't judge the politics.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Do you think it's going to be a potential problem if you run, your faith?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "OMNEY: Well, a lot of things are charged in politics, some accurate, some not.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "How do you respond to that charge?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I would reverse all of the policies that have made America one of the least friendly places to start new businesses and to grow business.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Most important thing to you?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "And can you come back maybe when you've got a bit more to say about your decision?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Piers, the most intense part of the storm is happening right now.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Rob, what's it like there?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "I lost ISP, so I assume we're done.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Have you seen that before?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "a couple of hours ago, Piers.", "docId": "110201pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "When did the shooting happen?", "qSentId": 482}]